[
	{
		"question": "A Pure Glow",
		"answer": "Paul Gower",
		"location": "Before Gower Quest, at the Gower Farm. After, at the Life Altar.",
		"challenge": "N/A"
	},
	{
		"question": "A Zen She",
		"answer": "Zenesha",
		"location": "East Ardougne's center square, in the platebody shop along its southern side.",
		"challenge": "Puzzle Box"
	},
	{
		"question": "Ace Match Elm",
		"answer": "Cam the Camel",
		"location": "North of Al Kharid, west of the Duel Arena.  No Camulet is needed to speak with the camel.",
		"challenge": "Puzzle Box"
	},
	{
		"question": "Ah; wet arm",
		"answer": "Amaethwr",
		"location": "Lletya's farming patch.",
		"challenge": "Lockbox"
	},
	{
		"question": "Aha Jar",
		"answer": "Jaraah",
		"location": "Al Kharid, Duel Arena's hospital/entrance.",
		"challenge": "N/A"
	},
	{
		"question": "An Paint Tonic",
		"answer": "Captain Ninto",
		"location": "Under White Wolf Mountain, in the bar. Requires the Fishing Contest quest.",
		"challenge": "Puzzle Box"
	},
	{
		"question": "Arc O Line",
		"answer": "Caroline",
		"location": "North Witchaven, next to the rowboat. After the Sea Slug quest, wanders the coast. After the Kennith's Concerns quest, found upstairs in her house directly west of the church.",
		"challenge": "11 (0 after Salt in the Wound)"
	},
	{
		"question": "Are Col",
		"answer": "Oracle",
		"location": "Ice Mountain's northern peak, west of Edgeville.",
		"challenge": "48"
	},
	{
		"question": "Arr! So I am a crust, and?",
		"answer": "Ramara du Croissant",
		"location": "Piscatoris Fishing Colony's furnace room; requires the Swan Song quest.",
		"challenge": "Puzzle Box"
	},
	{
		"question": "Bail Trims",
		"answer": "Brimstail",
		"location": "Tree Gnome Stronghold, in the cave west of the southern bank.",
		"challenge": "N/A"
	},
	{
		"question": "By Look",
		"answer": "Bolkoy",
		"location": "Tree Gnone Village's general store, up a ladder.",
		"challenge": "13"
	},
	{
		"question": "Boast B",
		"answer": "Sabbot",
		"location": "Burthorpe, in the dungeon to the north of the Warriors' Guild.  After the Death Plateau quest, he is in the chamber to the west.",
		"challenge": "N/A"
	},
	{
		"question": "C On Game Hoc",
		"answer": "Gnome Coach",
		"location": "West of the Grand Tree in Tree Gnome Stronghold, walking around outside the Gnome Ball course.",
		"challenge": "6"
	},
	{
		"question": "Dt Run B",
		"answer": "Brundt",
		"location": "Relleka's Longhall, in the center of town.",
		"challenge": "4"
	},
	{
		"question": "Eek Zero Op",
		"answer": "Zookeeper",
		"location": "Ardougne Zoo",
		"challenge": "40, +1 after Eagles' Peak, +1 after Hunt for Red Raktuber"
	},
	{
		"question": "El Ow",
		"answer": "Lowe",
		"location": "Varrock's archery store",
		"challenge": "N/A"
	},
	{
		"question": "Ergo I Dig Clay",
		"answer": "Celia Diggory",
		"location": "Varrock's digsite, just outside of the Empty Throne Room.",
		"challenge": "Tower Puzzle"
	},
	{
		"question": "Err Cure It",
		"answer": "Recruiter",
		"location": "West Ardougne's center square.",
		"challenge": "20"
	},
	{
		"question": "Goblin Kern",
		"answer": "King Bolren",
		"location": "Tree Gnome Village, next to the spirit tree.",
		"challenge": "N/A"
	},
	{
		"question": "Got A Boy",
		"answer": "Gabooty",
		"location": "Tai Bwo Wannai's center.",
		"challenge": "11"
	},
	{
		"question": "Gulag Run",
		"answer": "Uglug Nar",
		"location": "Just west of Jiggig, which is south of Castle Wars and East of Gu'Tanoth.",
		"challenge": "Puzzle Box"
	},
	{
		"question": "Halt Us",
		"answer": "Luthas",
		"location": "At the hut east of the banana plantation on Musa Point, Karamja.",
		"challenge": "33 (or None)"
	},
	{
		"question": "Hated",
		"answer": "Death",
		"location": "Death's office; touch the hourglass just north of Draynor's lodestone.",
		"challenge": "N/A"
	},
	{
		"question": "He Do Pose. It Is Cultrrl, Mk?",
		"answer": "Riki the Sculptor's model",
		"location": "East Keldagrim, inside of the gravestone shop.",
		"challenge": "Puzzle Box"
	},
	{
		"question": "Hear A Lady Rant",
		"answer": "Lady Trahaearn",
		"location": "Prifddinas, by the Seren stones in the Trahaearn District.",
		"challenge": "N/A"
	},
	{
		"question": "Icy Fe",
		"answer": "Fycie",
		"location": "Rantz's cave, south-east of Gu'Tanoth.",
		"challenge": "N/A"
	},
	{
		"question": "I Eat Its Chart Hints Do U",
		"answer": "Shiratti the Cusstodian",
		"location": "Nardah, in the building north of the fountain.",
		"challenge": "Puzzle Box"
	},
	{
		"question": "I Faffy Run",
		"answer": "Fairy Nuff",
		"location": "Before the quest A Fairy Tale II and after A Fairy Tale III: just north of the bank in Zanaris. Between A Fairy Tale II & III: get the certificate from the potion shelf in her house north of the bank, then use the fairy ring codes: air, dir, djq, ajs.",
		"challenge": "Puzzle Box"
	},
	{
		"question": "Im Krom",
		"answer": "Rommik",
		"location": "Rimmington, in the general store.",
		"challenge": "7"
	},
	{
		"question": "I SAW THE LIE",
		"answer": "Ali the Wise",
		"location": "Nardah, in the northernmost house.",
		"challenge": "N/A"
	},
	{
		"question": "Iz A Ammo Load for Mrs Yakkers",
		"answer": "Moldark, Emissary of Zamorak",
		"location": "Edgeville, north-east of the bank.",
		"challenge": "7 (3 after the quest Ritual of the Mahjarrat, but before Rebuilding Edgeville)"
	},
	{
		"question": "Land Doomd",
		"answer": "Odd Old Man",
		"location": "The limestone mine west of Paterdomus, east of Varrock, and north of the Digsite.",
		"challenge": "Puzzle Box"
	},
	{
		"question": "Lark In Dog",
		"answer": "King Roald",
		"location": "Varrock Palace, in the south-eastern section on the ground floor.",
		"challenge": "24"
	},
	{
		"question": "Me Am The Calc",
		"answer": "Cam the Camel",
		"location": "North of Al Kharid, west of the Duel Arena.  No Camulet is needed to speak with the camel.",
		"challenge": "Puzzle Box"
	},
	{
		"question": "Me if",
		"answer": "Femi",
		"location": "Tree Gnome Stronghold, just outside of the gates.",
		"challenge": "N/A"
	},
	{
		"question": "Nod med",
		"answer": "Edmond",
		"location": "East Ardougne, behind the north-westernmost house.",
		"challenge": "3"
	},
	{
		"question": "O Birdz A Zany En Pc",
		"answer": "Cap'n Izzy no Beard",
		"location": "Brimhaven, at the entrance to the agility arena.",
		"challenge": "33"
	},
	{
		"question": "O eastern wishes",
		"answer": "Sensei Seaworth",
		"location": "Tuai Leit, the south-western section of the center.",
		"challenge": "Towers Puzzle"
	},
	{
		"question": "Ok Co",
		"answer": "Cook",
		"location": "Lumbridge Castle, in the kitchen on the ground floor.",
		"challenge": "7"
	},
	{
		"question": "Or A Vile",
		"answer": "Valerio",
		"location": "Al Kharid, next to the dancers south-west of Citharede Abbey.",
		"challenge": "17"
	},
	{
		"question": "Or Zinc Fumes Ward",
		"answer": "Wizard Frumscone",
		"location": "Yanille, basement of the Wizard's Guild.  Boostable 66 Magic to enter.",
		"challenge": "Puzzle Box"
	},
	{
		"question": "Pin heir all in place",
		"answer": "Philipe Carnillean",
		"location": "Before the quest Carnillean Rising, in the Carnillean household in south-western East Ardougne.  After the quest, depends on Quest Points: [400+: TzHaar Fight Caves]. [350+: Piscatoris Fishing Colony's machine room]. [300+: Oldak's house in northwest Dorgesh-Kaan]. [250+: very bottom of Polypore Dungeon]. [200+: The Green Ghost Inn in Port Phasmatys]. [150+: Shilo Village, top floor of Paramaya's Inn]. [100+: Mountain Camp in the Fremennik Province]. [50+: Inside Ardougne's Combat Training Camp].",
		"challenge": "N/A"
	},
	{
		"question": "Peaty Pert",
		"answer": "Party Pete",
		"location": "North-eastern Falador, in the Party Room.",
		"challenge": "N/A"
	},
	{
		"question": "Profs Lose Wrong Pie",
		"answer": "Professor Onglewip",
		"location": "South of Draynor, on the ground floor of the Wizards' Tower.",
		"challenge": "Puzzle Box"
	},
	{
		"question": "R Ak Mi",
		"answer": "Karim",
		"location": "Al Kharid, Kebab shop south of the furnace.",
		"challenge": "5"
	},
	{
		"question": "Rebirth Not Ritually",
		"answer": "Brother Tranquility",
		"location": "Mos Le'Harmless docks or Harmony Island (during and after The Great Brain Robbery).",
		"challenge": "N/A"
	},
	{
		"question": "Red Art Tans",
		"answer": "Trader Stan",
		"location": "The southern Port Sarim docks, next to the charter ship.",
		"challenge": "Puzzle Box"
	},
	{
		"question": "Reign us if immortal",
		"answer": "Malignius Mortifier",
		"location": "South-east of the clan camp and north-west of Port Sarim, surrounded by elemental mages.",
		"challenge": "Lockbox"
	},
	{
		"question": "Sequin Dirge",
		"answer": "Queen Sigrid",
		"location": "If the quest Blood Runs Deep is completed, in the Miscellania Castle throne room.  Otherwise, in the throne room of Etceteria Castle.",
		"challenge": "Puzzle Box"
	},
	{
		"question": "Snah",
		"answer": "Hans",
		"location": "Outside of Lumbridge Castle (walks around the castle clockwise)",
		"challenge": "N/A"
	},
	{
		"question": "Soy Drain",
		"answer": "Ysondria",
		"location": "Lumbridge Swamp, at the Nexus.",
		"challenge": "8"
	},
	{
		"question": "Stab Ob",
		"answer": "Sabbot",
		"location": "Burthorpe, in the dungeon to the north of the Warriors' Guild.  After the Death Plateau quest, he is in the chamber to the west.",
		"challenge": "N/A"
	},
	{
		"question": "Taboo Rises Shyly",
		"answer": "Soothsayer Sybil",
		"location": "In The Heart of Gielinor (south-west of Nardah), outside of the entrance to Telos.",
		"challenge": "N/A"
	},
	{
		"question": "Them Cal Came",
		"answer": "Cam the Camel",
		"location": "North of Al Kharid, west of the Duel Arena.  No Camulet is needed to speak with the camel.",
		"challenge": "Puzzle Box"
	},
	{
		"question": "We Irk Over Namesake",
		"answer": "Ramokee Skinweaver",
		"location": "Polypore Dungeon, at the bottom.",
		"challenge": "N/A"
	},
	{
		"question": "Winsome Lad",
		"answer": "Wise Old Man",
		"location": "Draynor Village, in the house just north of the bank.",
		"challenge": "N/A"
	},
	{
		"question": "Winston Lane",
		"answer": "Nials Newton",
		"location": "Taverley, next to the lodestone.",
		"challenge": "10"
	}
]